<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ham Radio Duo</title>
    <description>CW and POTA. Adventure couple doing amateur radio, ham radio, CW, morse code, and POTA parks on the air.</description>
    <link>https://hamradioduo.com</link>
    <atom:link href="https://hamradioduo.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 05:21:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Print Your Own Case for The Just OK Mini</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/print-your-own-case-for-the-just-ok-mini/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/print-your-own-case-for-the-just-ok-mini/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 04:39:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>If you have one of our Just OK Minis, the ridiculously small 20m antenna, and a 3D printer, you can print this little case we made for it. just ok mini - holder just ok mini - holder.stl 213 KB .a{fill:none;stroke:currentColor;stroke-linecap:round;stroke-linejoin:round;stroke-width:1.5px;} download-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Contraption - 3D Files Available for the Preview Version</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/the-contraption-3d-files-available-for-the-preview-version/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/the-contraption-3d-files-available-for-the-preview-version/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The Contraption is a 3D printed case for creating a handheld HF radio out of a QRP radio + battery + antenna. It is ridiculous, but fun. With the Contraption, you can turn your QMX or QCX-mini (and someday CFT1) into a handheld portable HF 20m radio. For morse code, you can use a magnetic key mounte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KX2 vs Budget CW RIGs</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/kx2-vs-budget-cw-rigs/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/kx2-vs-budget-cw-rigs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:39:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>We took an Elecraft KX2 into the field and put it up against three less expensive CW rigs. Was the KX2 worth ten times the price? We ran POTA activations, ragchews, and side-by-side tests to find out. Spoiler: it was fun and there is something to love about all the radios. What we tested We used the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huntsville Hamfest: Why we ❤️ it!</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/huntsville-hamfest-why-we-it/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/huntsville-hamfest-why-we-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A summary of Hamfest 2025 from our perspective, as morse code lovers who camped for the full experience. Huntsville Hamfest: Why We Love It! Have you ever wondered why Huntsville Hamfest is such a big deal? It&apos;s legendary for being the &quot;Friendliest Hamfest in America,&quot; and we&apos;re here to show you why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunset to Moonlight 🌙 Morse Code POTA</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/sunset-to-moonlight-morse-code-pota/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/sunset-to-moonlight-morse-code-pota/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:58:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>We had a fun POTA starting at sunset and ending after dark. Testing a prototype antenna at Joe Wheeler State Park Hello to all our CW friends! This is another morse code parks on the air (POTA) activation at the beautiful Joe Wheeler State Park in Alabama. In our video, watch as we set up our gear u</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ultra-portable 20m antenna: pre-order</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/new-ultra-portable-20m-antenna-signup-for-early-access/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/new-ultra-portable-20m-antenna-signup-for-early-access/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 04:53:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>We designed a pocket sized, ridiculously small antenna for the 20 meter band in amateur radio. We initially created this page for people to sign up to get notified when it was available. We had a great response for people who purchased early adopter versions. That testing went great and we found a f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamfest Preview: Radio Museum!</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/hamfest-preview-radio-museum/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/hamfest-preview-radio-museum/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:31:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore the Signals Museum in Huntsville This week we had the honor to meet and interview Dr. Marc Bendickson who is the collector behind the new Signals Museum in Huntsville, AL. Just walking in the door you know it&apos;s going to be amazing. It&apos;s way more than just old radios; it&apos;s a treasure trove of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>✳️ New Morse Code Website and Discord Community Channel ✳️</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/new-morse-code-website-and-discord-community-channel/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/new-morse-code-website-and-discord-community-channel/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 19:55:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Join the new Morse Code Community! Are you interested in learning morse code or know someone who is?! Michael and I have launched a brand new website that’s your go-to place for all things related to Morse code. We created this to be a one stop link for anyone interested in Morse Code. https://learn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>📬 New!! QSL Card Service</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/new-qsl-card-service/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/new-qsl-card-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 03:56:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Automatically Print and Mail QSL Cards! We&apos;ve got something new to share that will make sending QSL cards super easy! If you&apos;ve ever made a new radio contact and then completely forgot to mail out a QSL card, then this is for you. Our new service lets you send a QSL card right from your phone or com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duo Straight Key ONE!!  Order your new Morse Code key now.</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/duo-straight-key-one-order-your-new-morse-code-key-now-2/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/duo-straight-key-one-order-your-new-morse-code-key-now-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:56:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Meet our latest creation: the Duo Straight Key ONE. We love straight keys. We recently restored a WWII-era J-38 and absolutely fell in love with the way that it felt. The long lever arm action provides a very smooth punchy feel as the letters just pop out. We wished we could tell everyone to go to t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasps and POTA?</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/wasps-and-pota/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/wasps-and-pota/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:01:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>CW POTA Activation by the Lake at Joe Wheeler State Park We love camping and hiking, and this is a great place for both. This beautiful park in Alabama is a mix of lake views and lush green beauty—perfect for enjoying nature while playing radio and CW. We hiked from our camper to explore around the </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunting POTA with a 2 ft Antenna!</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/hunting-pota-with-a-2-ft-antenna/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/hunting-pota-with-a-2-ft-antenna/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:43:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>We recently did a there-and-back trip to get our daughter from college in Florida. We made an adventure out of it, by playing radio pretty much the whole trip! It was a great excuse to stress test a new antenna we are working on, the &quot;Just OK Antenna&quot;. We&apos;re hoping to sort out some things and eventu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HF Ham Radio for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/hf-ham-radio-for-beginners/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/hf-ham-radio-for-beginners/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 06:19:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Hey, it’s Michael (N4FFF) and Becky (N4BKY) and we&apos;re diving into the exciting world of HF (High Frequency) ham radio for beginners. We recently had the opportunity to talk with a new ham about how &quot;lonely&quot; it was having not gotten to have any new contacts locally with his new technician class licen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Piece of Morse Code History!</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/we-got-a-piece-of-morse-code-history-2/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/we-got-a-piece-of-morse-code-history-2/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 02:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The J-38 Key Hi friends, it&apos;s Mike (N4FFF) and Becky (N4BKY) from HamRadioDuo! If you&apos;ve been following our journey, you already know about our deep appreciation for Morse code. Recently, something very special found its way into our shack—a genuine, vintage J-38 straight key. Part of the magic of m</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is your fist?</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/how-is-your-fist/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/how-is-your-fist/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 05:22:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>CW Morse Code Checker Tool Of course we don&apos;t mean how is your literal fist, but how is your CW fist? Becky recently got a new Vibroplex Bug from the &apos;60s. One of the first steps was to adjust everything and make sure that it works well. After watching some videos online, and one in particular from </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing some Boy Scouts to Morse Code and Parks On The Air (POTA)</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/introducing-some-boy-scouts-to-morse-code-and-parks-on-the-air-pota/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/introducing-some-boy-scouts-to-morse-code-and-parks-on-the-air-pota/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 04:36:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Monte Sano State Park: A Perfect Spot Monte Sano State Park in Alabama is a beautiful place and a great location to find a new spot for our latest POTA activation. The park offers amazing views and lots of hiking trails that any adventurer would love. But this time, we weren&apos;t alone! Boy Scout Troop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seconds to Deploy Challenge</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/seconds-to-deploy-challenge/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/seconds-to-deploy-challenge/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 04:17:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Hey there, radio friends! Welcome to our &quot;Seconds to Deploy Challenge!&quot; Imagine a race where the only way to win is to have the quickest deploy. We&apos;re trying to make it easier to play radio, where the goal is to set up a tiny portable station as quickly as possible. Setting Up Lightning Fast Join us</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morse Code in Athens, AL</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/morse-code-in-athens-al/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/morse-code-in-athens-al/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>We do a POTA Activation in Athens, Alabama Today, Becky (N4BKY) and I had a delightful Parks on the Air (POTA) activations in the charming town of Athens, Alabama. This spontaneous adventure brought us to a picturesque public park nestled right along the historic Trail of Tears, surrounded by the be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morse Code Tools | CW Practice and Games! 🤖</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/morse-code-tools-cw-practice-and-games/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/morse-code-tools-cw-practice-and-games/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:20:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Hello, fellow Morse code fans! Michael and Becky from the HamRadioDuo here. Today, we&apos;re diving into the world of Morse Code tools that make learning fun and exciting. If you&apos;re curious about how to make practicing CW a blast, you&apos;re in the right place! We’ve got some cool stuff to share that&apos;s goin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CW Lake POTA Activation on our G90</title>
      <link>https://hamradioduo.com/cw-lake-pota-activation-on-our-g90/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://hamradioduo.com/cw-lake-pota-activation-on-our-g90/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 23:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover Lake Guntersville State Park Lake Guntersville State Park is a wonderful favorite spot in Alabama. It&apos;s a great place to camp and play radio. We found a pavilion by the lake, providing a picture-perfect backdrop for a Parks on the Air (POTA) adventure. We had a great time and definitely rec</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>